northcountrynow.com 2019-05-31

# NorthCountryNow.com Privacy Notice | NorthCountryNow

### NorthCountryNow.com Privacy Notice

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at the bottom of every page.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the NorthCountryNow.com website. On some pages, you can place a classified ad, make requests for advertising information and submit news items, photos, links and comment. You can also enter occasional contests. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include:

        Name  
        Address  
        Email address  
        Phone number  
        Credit/Debit Card Information

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing a classified ad only to complete that order and charge for the ad. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide when requesting advertising information or submitting news items, photos, links and comment only to confirm the identity of the submitter. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use information you submit when entering contests to pick a winnner of the contest. If at the time you enter your name in a contest you indicate you would like to receive occasional e-mails from NorthCountryNow.com featuring offers, coupons and special deals from local businesses, your name and e-mail address will be entered into a database used for that purpose. All e-mails will only be sent by NorthCountryNow.com and your name and identifying information will not be shared with other businesses or organizations.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women entered our contest or took our survey, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Third-party ads, primarily provided by Google, also appear on our website. Google may use non-identifying and aggregate information to serve up future ads based on your browsing history and to relay to advertisers.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting North Country This Week, P.O. Box 975, 19 Depot St., Potsdam, NY 13676 either in person, by U.S. mail, by telephone at 315-265-1000 or by e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#196d71706a6e7c7c725957766b6d715a766c776d6b6057766e377a7674).

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact North Country This Week, P.O. Box 975, 19 Depot St., Potsdam, NY 13676 either in person, by U.S. mail, by telephone at 315-265-1000 or by e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3a4e5253494d5f5f517a5455484e5259554f544e484354554d14595557).

Effective December 20, 2008
